- Really?
- Really.
Look! That's her!
Kannawa from the Publicity Department!
The poster she proposed
won an advertising award.
THERE IN A FLASH! PLUMBER
PUBLICITY DPT - KOSUKE HITA
Okay!
Good morning.
PUBLICITY DPT - MINORI TAMANA & RIN SUZUGAYA
- Good morning.
PUBLICITY DPT - MIHARU SATO
PUBLICITY DPT - MISAKI TANAKA
- Good morning.
Morning!
Good morning.
PUBLICITY DPT - KAORU HISAYAMA
- Morning, everyone!
- Good morning.
Good morning.
Kannawa-san...
About SQ's web announcement...
We can no longer hire "Tsuru-san,"
the influencer we booked.
PUBLICITY DPT - AZUSA KANNAWA
- What should we do?
- You're the one in charge of this.
PUBLICITY DPT - AZUSA KANNAWA
- Before coming to me with questions,
isn't it on you to prepare a proposal?
Y-Yes.
If we need a stand-in, use your
available resources to find one.
Tell the other party we'll contact
them by the end of the day.
Th-Thank you so much.
Oh, man...
I've corrected the necessary
documents to send to Planning.
- What?!
- Whoa, you did?
Thank you so much.
How do you expect to get any work
done with your desk in that state?
- Clean it up.
- Yes, ma'am!
Kannawa-san.
- Can I speak with you?
- Yes.
Kannawa-san is as cool as ever today.
I think you mean "scary."
She's not wrong, but there are
nicer ways of saying things.
PUBLICITY DPT HEAD - EIJI KUROKAWA
- As I told you a while ago,
- a newbie is joining our department as of today.
- Yes.
- I'd like to put you in charge of training him.
Me?
Look, I understand that
you've got your hands full.
But this new kid's exceptional.
Just between you and me,
he was the top scorer on the exam!
I see...
Which is why we want you,
the Publicity Department's ace,
to whip him into shape!
I understand.
We had him look over the
new hire training materials,
and he was able to absorb everything so well.
And his responses were so lively...
I really don't wanna!
Why's it gotta be me, of all people?
My communication skills ain't good.
Surely the boss realizes
I don't fit in at the office...
Guess not.
For better or for worse, he can be so dense.
I finally established myself as
"the one who refuses to go out drinking,
so don't bother inviting her."
Kannawa-san?
Forget it. She never joins us.
Things were finally getting easier.
Teaching the newbie how to do his job
isn't the only thing I'll have to do.
Good morning!
Oh, Kamegawa-kun.
I'm sorry for arriving late!
I was cleaning up my probationary desk.
Oh, sorry. Did I interrupt?
Kamegawa-kun, this here
is your mentor, Kannawa-san.
NEW RECRUIT - YU KAMEGAWA
- It's nice to meet you! I'm Yu Kamegawa!
- Yeah... Oh, I'm sorry!
I only need to use my surname
in these instances, right?
I'm Azusa Kannawa. It's nice to meet you.
Yes! I'll be in your care, Kannawa-senpai!
I expect great things of you, Kamegawa-kun!
What a good kid.
- Well, I'll leave the rest to you, Kannawa-san.
- He's got this friendly charm to him.
Yes, sir.
So I'll be in charge of taking this young man,
new to the industry, under my wing.
It's a heavy task, but I gotta do my best.
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
EPISODE 1: ME? THE MENTOR?!
- "Me? The Mentor?!"
I'm sure you heard plenty about our
company during new-employee training.
Though we started out
developing video games,
nowadays we've expanded into books,
apparel, real estate, and more.
That means there are many more projects
for the Publicity Department to handle.
If anything is unclear,
talk to me immediately.
Yes, ma'am!
My desk is here.
- And yours is next to mine.
- Yes, ma'am!
- This is the kitchen. Bring your own cup.
- The copy machine.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Behind me is the printing paper.
- Y-Yes!
- The nearest bathroom!
- Y-Yes, ma'am!
SWEET POTATO PIE
Snacks from business trips are stashed here.
You're free to take whatever you want.
Th-Thank you.
I guess that covers everything.
Other places I need to show him are...
Thank you so much for giving me a tour.
Can I ask you if there's anything
I need help with?
Yes. Please do so.
All right. I think I was able to
teach him the important stuff.
- Um, Senpai...
- What is it?
Oh, excuse me, but...
I was wondering what I'm
supposed to do for today.
I needed to teach him how to do his job!
I'm about to go to a meeting with a client.
I'll have you join me.
U-Understood!
You only need to shadow me
and observe the meeting.
But before that...
- Let's practice exchanging business cards.
- Yes, ma'am.
You don't need to focus too hard
on business manners,
but you should make it a habit
to get used to the basics—
Here you go, Senpai.
Please allow our newcomer
to join the meeting today.
I'm Kamegawa. It's nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you, Kamegawa-san.
A refreshing greeting...
AZUSA KANNAWA
- A smooth business card exchange...
Whereas I, the mentor,
exchanged my cards with the floor...
Based on the research shown,
we would like to disseminate
the information on social media.
I need to at least maintain my dignity
as a mentor while I'm working.
I appreciate him looking at me so sincerely,
but I'm getting nervous
from him staring so much...
No. Every move I make as a mentor
affects the new recruit's development!
This is no time to be nervous!
It's no use! I'm so nervous!
- Good work in there, Kannawa-senpai.
- Yeah...
I'm tired.
Not from work, but from the
heavy burden of being a mentor.
It's almost time for lunch.
As his mentor, I'm the one who needs
to extend the invitation, right?
The family restaurant I often
went to with Senpai could work.
Isn't it considered workplace harassment for
a senior to ask their junior out to lunch?
But if I don't invite him,
it's like I'm sending the message of "I don't
plan on getting friendly with you," right?
What'll we even talk about?
The weather?
Stocks?
Daily conversations are
the toughest topic fer me!
Senpai?
I! I'm going to a meeting now!
So have your lunch while I do that.
U-Understood.
What was I thinking, running away?
- I'll be heading out now.
- 'Kay.
"'Kay"? Just "'kay"?
I could have said a word
of appreciation or two.
Thank you for today.
I'm not sure if I did well since I was so
nervous, it being my first day and all...
No newbie is perfect
their first day on the job.
I suppose not.
You can rely on me going forward.
- That's what mentors are for.
- Yes, ma'am!
I look forward to working with you
tomorrow as well, Kannawa-senpai!
'Kay.
Good work!
Good work today!
How did it go?
I was nervous, but thanks to
everyone, I think I managed.
He was nervous?
Of course he was.
Even if he's the top scorer,
he's still a newbie.
I'm no good.
All I did was worry about myself.
I need to be a reliable senpai.
For starters, I need to
be more frank with him.
Hey, Kamegawa-kun.
What prefecture are you from?
I'm from Saitama.
What? Me, too! Where in Saitama?
- Over in Kawaguchi—
- Hey!
You're in the way. Move.
I'm sorry!
I did it! I greeted them properly!
Today, I'll have you write up a proposal
for a small company's manga app.
Yes, ma'am.
I've prepared samples of my
past work proposals for you.
You can use those for reference.
Yes, ma'am. Thank you so much.
Just you wait.
Today'll be the day I invite you to lunch!
Um, Kannawa-senpai?
What?
I sent you my proposal in the work chat.
Would you look it over for me?
It's too wordy. Keep your concepts
concise and easy to understand.
Yes, ma'am. I'll fix it right away.
- You can do that after lunch.
- Yes, ma'am.
This is it! This feels so natural!
Okay, now's my chance!
Huh?
Whoopsy-daisy.
Hot, hot, hot...
Kannawa-senpai?
You think that's adequate?
Minding your health is also part of the job!
You're right. I'm sorry!
I'm on a budget, so...
I-Is that so?
I totally missed the timing.
On top of that, he's broke...
Reduced to eatin' a single cup of ramen...
He's got me worryin' about him!
How can a senior foster their juniors
if they can't even invite them to lunch?
Kanna.
What are you sighing about?
It's going to be fine.
You're doing your best.
Being straightforward is your strong suit.
I'm sure everyone will see that someday.
I guarantee it.
Kanzaki-senpai...
KANKAIJI
Understood. I'll explain that
to the other party.
You're a lifesaver!
Goes to show that what one
really needs is a reliable colleague!
Was that all you had to say?
You should try small talk sometime.
Oh, I know!
That collab café we worked on?
There's gonna be a second installment.
I think you'll be hearing back
about work there soon.
I see.
Something on your mind?
Just that this might be a good opportunity
to try out the new recruit.
Yeah!
Oh, you're his mentor, right?
To think that someone like Kannawa,
who was trained by Kanzaki-senpai,
would be the next to train others.
What do you mean, "someone like"?
Don't be too harsh on the newbie.
And be sure to communicate with him.
It's no problem.
I was able to greet him today,
and I tried to invite him to lunch!
For your information, "'kay" and "yeah" aren't
proper conversations. You know that, right?
Of course I do!
I'm worried.
You know how often people
change jobs nowadays, right?
Change jobs?!
He's right. That's possible.
Oh! How about you try reading
self-improvement books?
You know, stuff like,
A MUST-READ FOR MANAGERS! A CAPABLE BOSS
- "A capable boss doesn't
scold their subordinates!"
No need.
Other people's success stories
won't necessarily be helpful to me.
Good work today.
Oh! I forgot to buy dinner!
And after I told him that minding
your health is part of the job...
BOOM! VEGGIES
- Veggies, check.
A CAPABLE BOSS
"Communication skills to be the best boss."
"Greetings are fundamental to communication."
"Smile brightly."
You're in the way. Move.
Move.
G-Good morning, Kamegawa!
Scary!
If I greeted him like that,
he'd think something was up!
"Communicating with your
subordinates in a strict tone is outdated."
"Instead, for them to grow, praise your
subordinates over and over again..."
"Correct them when they
need to be corrected..."
Huh?
So when exactly do I praise him?
Or correct him?
Proactive communication
increases productivity...
You can't communicate with subordinates
over drinks in this day and age...
What am I supposed to do?
I never thought I'd have to
pay the price for giving up on
smoothly communicating
with people like this.
Oh, no! My noodles are overdone!
BOOM! VEGGIES
Shoot!
- All set!
- A mentor being late? Unbelievable!
I only crammed for one night...
But all I can do is take it one step at a time.
Getting used to the job?
- Yes, just a bit...
- Greet with a smile.
- Oh! Senpai!
G-Good—
Kannawa-san's his mentor?
I feel sorry for that newcomer.
She can be strict.
GENERAL AFFAIRS - AKEMI HAMAWAKI
- She always looks angry, so she's scary.
Well, I think she gets away with it
because she's good at her job.
What? But it's difficult to work with her.
INTERACTING WITH YOUR JR: -GREET WITH BRIGHT SMILE!
-EXPLAIN SIMPLY! -AVOID HARSH LANGUAGE!
Oh, no! Are you all right, Senpai?
I'm glad she wasn't my mentor.
Um...
Oh, sorry.
Sorry. It's almost time to start the day.
- Let's go.
- I'm glad!
I get to know Kannawa-senpai's kinder side.
I feel a bit luckier than most!
I-Is that so?
Oh, no. Kannawa-san's here.
Sorry, I overstepped.
- I'm not going to thank you.
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank you...
Huh? Did you say something?
- Nothing! Let's go!
- Yes, ma'am!
Kamegawa. For today's lunch—
I'm having a veggie stick with it today!
I see...